Ugh
What is it? Was it a kid?
When I looked for it, it wasn't there
Why now?
Show up two months late
Ugh, ugh
- Traveler's father
- Yes
Uh huh, stay still, stay still
Right now
prepare for return
Yes?
It's still a while before the paru rings.
Ah
Kid...
Looks like you got all your sleep today
I will enter the palace as soon as the blue bell rings.
Oh, but what's going on?
Jimjo is still there
It looks like it's in the upper left hand.
don't move away
Whoa, whoa
gone, bee
I went
Ha...
I turned
I'm crazy
Ah...
Ah, um...
Um...
Wow
Well
Oh my!
Um...
Um, um...
Mr. Aggie, no.
Mr. Bean, don’t you have any sleep?
How come you walk here every morning?
That you have become Mr. Bean’s mom
Congratulations...
Still shaking like this
You are about to have a national wedding.
Let go of the past
Degrade and harm
If you don't pay a tribute
You have to live as Mr. Bean for decades
She's not the crown prince's wife.
What is that...
If you do
Why did you enter the palace?
You used that gun as an excuse
Not wanting to enter the palace
Are you saying you are going to abandon Prince Jeun?
Because I had no choice but to do it
Are you going to make excuses for me again?
I think you're mistaken
I'll tell you
you never loved me
Then what I did was
What we did during those long years
What is it?
pity, admiration
I misunderstood it as love
sadness, foolishness
If you call that kind of thing love
Don’t you feel so sorry for your love?
If you don't get swayed by me anymore
How about this?
The crown prince took the backpack
I brought it into the inner hall.
How can a woman become an eunuch?
Where are you?
Where is that child now?
Are you so worried with that look on your face?
I make a decision
What?
Whether the crown prince gets hurt or the child gets hurt
Whether we're both hurt
This is everything
It's because of the great army
Well, if you delay any longer,
You're really late.
I'll go in
Uh, Mr. Bean
- Confess it
- Don't tell me
Nari, Jeundaegun
- Confess it
- I told you not to tell!
Mr. Bin didn't even show his respect.
How could it be without a message?
Do you go to the East Palace?
I broke the law anyway
Shall we try to break it somewhere?
what?
Baby, you're noisy, baby
- Ugh!
- Oh, why, what, huh?
evil!
No, that, that, no, that, that
That's not it...
Get Mr. Bean out.
I...
Please go, Mama Bean.
Oh my, oh my
Oh my, what's going on
Everyone please go away.
If I reveal what happened today
I will bow to you, understand?
- Yes, I understand.
- Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Go, go
Hurry up and go
Hey! Why are you here?
What did you do to me?
What are you doing!
It wouldn't be unfair if I did, Mr.
Hey, and
- whamma
- This is my body now?
Mr.
Like ‘you are me and I am you’
Such a sweet conversation
Is it time to share, now?
I also saw my nephew
I also saw everything about Mr. Bean.
In other people’s eyes, this is
It's navy blue, my dear.
Mr. I
please
do nothing
I sprinkled ashes on the finished rice.
What is there for Mr. Bean to see?
What should I do?
Bakgadal is that child
Wouldn't that be dangerous?
Living in the palace for 50 years
I realized something
Rather than taking a chance
How important it is to avoid risk
After the Crown Prince
Wouldn't it be nice if I took her as a concubine?
It's best to stay still for now.
You are wise too
I realize by knocking
Ah, yes
Ah, kid, still
Well, Mr. Bean’s mom is crazy.
Because you know she’s a woman.
So I'm more anxious
The woman who shot the crown prince in the heart
What can't people do?
What does that mean?
Gun reason?
The person who made a hole in my heart
Vinssi mamayeyu?
Didn't I tell you?
Ah, still
Now the two of you are gentle
You solved it, right?
Pick up a gun again
In this heart of hearts
There's no need to drill a hole, right?
There must be?
be careful
It's your body now
Tusk, father
Ji Gayu
This unfilial woman
Gayu first
mama
What did you draw from earlier?
Are you thinking deeply?
There are less than 50 days left until the national wedding.
You're not thinking of anything else, are you?
What are you going to do?
Don't worry
not me
Because my nephew will move
‘Jojo Sang-gung’s nephew’?
Manufactured Sanggung Cho Noodles
Aren't you from the Great Gamma?
But why are you taking the lead?
Rumors that will harm you
Do you want to pay?
He's just like me
- It would be foolish.
- That's right.
I ate three
Have you heard the news?
What is it? What news?
What I say really needs to be kept a secret.
Yeah
Last night...
New here this time
Donggung Palace’s inner circle and crown prince
They said we slept together
- Really? Are you crazy?
- Uh
Ah, then
Why are you reading romance novels like this?
The reality is even worse, it’s red pepper paste.
So, I mean
Boy, really
What, it's not fun anymore
Because reality is more fun
Boy, really
mama
Now, a flue has arrived from Saga.
Lord Jeundae, Nari...
Why Prince Jeun?
Ha, what are you doing now?
I'm collecting it
the warmth I gave
Peace, pure love, all
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
Please don't do anything
I asked for it, but
It's getting worse
Make a scandal about the moon?
Why are you smiling?
What's on my face?
no
I didn't bury it
In fact, I had rice on the corner of my mouth.
Did you know?
Woohee you
Didn’t you say you buried it?
If you didn't bury it, you didn't bury it.
If you bury it
Yes, it's been buried since then.
You still don’t know me!
Those who brought down my brother
Do you think I'll sit there?
That's right
I don't know anything anymore
no, you know
what do i want
What is my earnestness?
What wasn't love
It's not me, it's the commander.
what kind of man
The woman he loves
Being someone else's woman
Would you like it desperately?
yes
It was a stroke from my youth.
Now let's go our separate ways
yes
I'll do whatever you want.
It will be the Crown Princess
It will be a mid-game battle too.
Someday, I will take over Daebijeon as well.
I followed all the steps
I will step on it as I should.
Just those times
I think I'll try pulling it.
If both the chief minister and the crown prince die,
Anyway, the dragon and dragon
I have to go to the great general.
- You...
- In contrast to the main statue,
Greetings every morning
We'll meet face to face
As we promised someday
With gray hair and wrinkled appearance
We'll grow old together
That's enough for me
we now
let's never see each other again
please
I am now
you are so horrible
When it gets cold here too
Where do I go now?
Your Majesty is also seated
the moon looks for you
We will try to resolve this situation.
Ha, get me out of the palace.
For the time being, at Jeundaegun’s private residence.
Don't hide yourself
No matter how severe the injury is
Without justification, the Grand Prince’s private residence
Because you won't be able to fall behind
No, by the way, the great queen mama
Can you please stay still?
I brought you in
If it's revealed that you're a mama
Sparks will fly to Mama too
You probably won't move for a while.
I go to Boryeong
You're evacuating your family.
while I'm away
I'm holding on well
Ha!
majesty!
Destroy the crown prince who indulged in sodomy
Please correct the example of the country.
Please correct it.
Your Highness!
The crown prince is dark blue
Who dare say such terrible things
Do you mean to say it?
Degradation to scandal
The inner coffin that was enveloped
It is said that his identity was stolen and he entered office.
I'm looking for the police officer.
After the arrest
Let me tell you the truth myself
Put the scandal to rest
Please do so.
Those who started the rumor right away
I want foot color
caused the crown prince to be embroiled in scandal
Catch that eunuch.
Yes, Your Highness
- The mother-in-law
- Yes, Nari.
Have you seen someone like this?
I'm not sure
Take a good look
‘The crown prince does not pray’
The person who said
Why are you acting like that these days?
It's not even funny
Praying to a tree or something?
Well, the guy called Sky.
You have to have a conscience
If you have a minimum of conscience
You can't do this to me.
You took everything from me
Even poverty and my body
So this prayer is a bit...
Please listen
Then now you can swear too
Because I won’t hold any grudges
This child's body is a little
Please protect me
please
Save me, inspiration.
maybe even inspiration
It may be dangerous, but
the moon
Please
Please save me
It's my daughter's lifesaver.
How could the ledger pretend not to know?
tell me
How can I help you?
With these, my family
Please evacuate
please take me away
If you do this, I will only believe in inspiration.
Without even filling up my meals
I can't even see my family's faces
Now that I know that I have left the palace,
The left injury is going to hit my back.
Me and the guest family are together
If anyone even sees it
You might get angry
Before you get caught for no reason
We have to hurry
When I looked at it, I couldn’t even walk.
The moon is like this
How did you endure it?
The life of running away
It's hard work too
That it's a lonely thing
I didn't know
What do you mean by that?
Dal-i is the old man’s wife’s niece?
Please ask the moon
I wonder if Dal is in danger
I guess I'll have to hide that kid behind me
So, you guys also organize the accommodation.
Take shelter for a moment
Dal-i is becoming dangerous?
Where is that child now?
I can't explain it to you
Until you explain
Not even one step from here
won't move
Even if I die, I won't move
So please tell me!
No, what does that mean, huh?
Cut back and forth and suddenly
Dal-i is not our daughter.
my stomach hurts
Even if you are not a child
The years we lived as parents and children
It's been five years
Ah, now without a proper explanation
Stealing someone else's daughter without any hesitation
Where are you!
no time to explain
It's better not to know
From now on
You two, you two, go your separate ways.
Who gets the money and when?
You are the sky
Samshin?
The moon and our parents and children
Even though you were the one who made the connection
It's up to us to break it off!
- that's right!
- Dal went to Hanyang!
take the child
I'm leaving Joseon
You two could be in danger.
I can't explain everything, but
The secret that Dal has
Bigger and more dangerous than Dono
So?
When the moon first entrusts you
The lady said that, right?
Look normal like everyone else
To live as a family of three
Lee Yi said it was sweet.
Although he secretly felt sorry for me
I liked it
Even if I live normally
It's like permission to say it's okay
So I keep going
The moon will live as a mother
Even if it becomes dangerous
I decided to live like that
Yes!
We originally specialized in braiding.
Jipaljikorn
Where are you going?
Whether you twist straw sandals or twist your arms
So much so that people don't like it
I will live happily ever after
Let's go together
Hey, take the lead!
My daughter is in danger!
Ha, Lieutenant Commander
I caught a court lady who caused a scandal.
kill me
That's the court lady
I am the nephew of the manufacturing chief.
Who's behind it?
There is no mastermind
It seems like just an immature rumor.
Well, a fact that doesn't exist at all
I didn't even say it
Hmm
What should I do?
Manufacturer, that person
I wrote enough
Aunt
Why on earth
why did you do that
Why do you do something like that?
It's unfair.
It was Mr. Bin who tried to kill the crown prince.
It was Mr. Bean who told me to send in a surprise attack.
Daewangdaebimado
Even though I ordered it knowing everything
Why is only old man Do Seung-ji sent into exile?
Why only old man Do Seung-ji?
Why are you going into exile?
You...
You can't believe it
yes
This is my friend
He's my son
Captain
please take care of my nephew
Please save me
I thought I would use you for a long time, but
It's a shame
bakgadali
I found out about that backpack seller.
When the Crown Prince's interest left
What can that child do?
Why is the Crown Prince suddenly interested?
Would you have left?
In one day
The inner coffin that resembles an abandoned person is
Where did it appear?
The inner view is
Have you caught it yet?
I'm looking for you, Your Majesty.
But if you catch the inner coffin,
What are you going to do?
Are you going to be true?
I have to be true
Please receive my order.
degradation
Yes?
The interior
Please give it to me, my dear.
What do you mean?
The Crown Prince reveals his inner view
Are you saying you tried to hide it?
Oh, uh...
I apologize.
Please kill me, my dear.
Ah, it's okay.
Let the left wing bring their swords
Yes, yes?
Ka, why is the knife, why, why...
How dare you attack your dragon gun
Disloyalty that spilled tea
You should ask
Ah...
I just spilled a cup of tea
Disloyalty?
a knife
Bring it
bring it
Your Highness!
I'm protecting it now
Do you know that that child will live forever?
Protect it now
Isn’t there a next time?
So
bakgadali
After that child too
Did you hide it?
Did you think I didn’t know?
The interior
no
That woman
That bakga is the moon
What does this all mean?
A woman?
Is it true what is said on the left?
Hello
Why is there no one?
Ah, hey!
Ouch
Ouch, Mr. Lee, Mr. Lee, Mr.
Baby, kinda, shit, tsk
I just grabbed a woman's wrist
Being chased
Where are you wandering around like that?
Then what if it becomes dangerous?
Are you Hong Gil-dong?
Once a woman, then a man
He was a backpacker, then he was a naekwan, and then he was a backpacker.
That's also from Queen Mother.
I was caught and had no choice...
Done
Rather, at that dawn
Why did you come to the East Palace?
No way, a little while ago, I was a Cheongguk person.
Maybe he brought some bad news
Are you an errand boy?
How could you...
My brother even said that
You said you did it?
Ah, well...
Yes, the Gyesannyeon incident, Jimjo, etc.
Because I know it better than anyone else
You can tell me.
Maybe the office
Have you got any news?
How can I believe you?
Would you like to tell that important story?
I will tell my brother directly.
Don't ask anymore
No, you should tell them.
Why do you say it's of no use...
Hahaha
What would I do if I heard it now?
Thanks to Mojiri
Oh no
What are you doing, let's go out
Hey, it's my house.
Wow, a guy who knows everything
For the time being, stay behind the Grand Prince.
Let's hide, okay?
the moon is you
Do you want to hide behind me for the rest of your life?
Chi
To be chased all my life
In the temple, in front of the shaman,
Why don't you start a ritual?
No, stay by my side.
marry me
What bullshit?
If you marry me
The picture on the left is also about you
will close the border
yes
Because you know everything about me
I won't hide it
If I keep leaving you behind
Will my brother give up on this revenge?
My resentment toward Woohee grows.
I'm worried that this national marriage will be broken off.
It's good that you're safe
I am glad that this national wedding is going well.
think about it
Hey, Grand Prince.
Come to your senses
I protect this body
The aftereffects of the crown prince falling into the water
I guess it hasn't healed yet.
I hope you understand.
lower body
If it's a foolish thing to do
God, a hundred times, a thousand times
I will be on your side, but
Just one chance
You have a different mind
If you have it
The Gyesannyeon incident
Guaranteed it won't happen again
Where could it be?
upper left
Are you looking for this?
My father is still
I'm using you
you help me
Also trying to kill the crown prince
He also gave me the crown prince's letter.
You probably knew everything
What a strange person.
No matter how dangerous it is, if it is useful
Because you won't abandon me
You and me too
Jimjodo
give me that child
If you do
the child dies
If you really feel like it, make it into government money.
I'll let you live your life
No way
puppy
Don't confront the left person
The Gyesannyeon incident
It's not over yet
The queen and my father-in-law who died for you
And think of poverty
Just because of one visit
복수도 미래도 모두 버릴 셈이냐
'Revenge'...
For that purpose, I
Kill the heavy warrior
Because it was put on the poor person.
So instead of taking revenge,
Didn’t you choose suicide?
weakly
Use it for yourself in the future
When left and right fell
Before the Great King
To avoid losing power
You need a weapon too
Take it out here
I'm sorry, Abama.
come out and see
What are you talking about now?
No...
Chugukjangga, Gasiraguyu
In front of everyone
Why don't you punish me?
The sodomy scandal will also subside.
Your Majesty has looked into the situation
If I go now, you will end me as a slave.
The hardships right now
I know you will do it.
No, there is no other way.
However, the body must
I'll put it back, okay?
And I was originally a slave too.
Even if you say you'll be a slave again
Well, it's nothing.
While traveling between Boryeong and Hanyang
I ran day and night
I was afraid I would get caught if I stayed.
But still I
My mind was worse than my body.
Because you've lived like this your whole life
But
There is nothing to be unfair about
Why are you so stupid!
Then ujjayu
If you don't bring me
I'm dealing with a left hand injury.
Take revenge on the poor woman right now.
I heard that everything is going to be ruined in the future.
Every day you
How did you feel when you opened and closed your eyes?
I dreamed of maps so I knew everything.
How did you get there?
Damn my future!
Don't cry with that face
Even if I tell you not to cry
I'll solve it
So pop, huh?
What
How are you going to solve it?
dog fight
why are you here
What are you doing?
I have come to take you to the seated table.
What?
How can they look so similar?
What did I do so wrong?
A woman lies about her identity
Since I entered the palace as a naegwan,
According to Gyeongguk Daejeon, it was for the crime of deceiving the palace.
For over 100 people
It is a type of exile and labor.
The law is quite systematic.
Okay
You have to follow it, Puck.
In this noble palace
Because I committed such a deception
I'm going to get beaten anyway
They say they feel like they’re going to die
Can I ask you one question?
Maybe he harasses a woman
To the man who tried to forcefully get drunk
What punishment is imposed?
Well, you know that.
‘Gyeongguk Daejeon’, ‘Daemyeongryul’
What does it say there?
Ah
Well, it's really...
According to ‘Daemyeongryul’
This is a crime of obscenity
Forcibly harassing a woman
When engaging in sexually humiliating behavior
Taehyung 50s to 80s
80 to 100 units long
can get off
Also, in the case of noblemen
Imprisonment or deprivation of public office
For royals or high-ranking officials
Depending on the sentence, the death penalty is possible.
The person called Hyeongpan
I can't memorize even a single law, oops
Like that
Oh, really?
Well then let me just make one complaint.
Ijo Panther standing over there
In front of Donhwamun
They harass me in public
I have untied my clothes.
Are you okay with this?
Oh my goodness
no
No, what nonsense, huh?
uh? Are you a backpack seller?
How are you going to solve it?
dog fight
I saw it
I saw it clearly with my own two eyes
Child, left superior
That's not it, I mean this...
A person named Yifan
Only when you reveal your side like that
Without hair
That kind of illness is
I, the person in charge of military power
The food that was stolen is
Well, you seem very proud?
This is what came out of this boat, this is everything
Military rations, military rations
no, what
Are you framing me like that?
It was Hopan who stole the military provisions.
I sold my military exemption certificate, um...
No, why are you still?
Splash shit on me?
What, am I just trash?
Hanseong Panyun received bribes.
I heard they only gamble
Is gambling a problem?
Accept bribes from shamans and magicians
It's better than giving it away
Daejehak said,
Neo-Confucianism wails, wails
Oh, no, that's...
Everything
Did you do it?
Only the innocent ones here
throw stones at me
Oh, well
I guess that's right, but whatever.
Yes, it eats up the country
We have to catch the rats.
Ministers who have problems
I will expose all your sins and punish them.
Left opponent...
Left, left counterpart
Hmm...
I'm sorry
Today is the moon
Punish me first
If you really care
Made with government fees
I'll let you live your life
If you get hit 100 times, you'll die.
It's no different
Instead, I'll send it away
I'm sending it to Tamna as government expenses.
Let’s finish it.
Tamra rani
What are the official expenses?
That would be good for you too.
You will soon become a national leader.
If that kid gets hit in the gut and dies
People leave Mr. Bean
I'm going to beat you to the punch.
Please protect Mr. Bin’s pride.
degradation
Tamra?
What are government expenses?
Please excuse me, sir.
You must punish me yourself
The scandal subsides.
degradation
Don't confront the left person
The queen and my father-in-law who died for you
And think of poverty
Ha...
Bar...
That, ba, bak, bak, bak ga dal-i
In Tamra...
Tamraro...
Please give me your majesty!
please release this child
I'm sorry.
It's none of your business.
no
It's something I'll be involved in.
This kid is mine
Give it to me
What are you doing?
I've seen degradation since I was born
Because of degradation
If someone loses their life
I can't buy it
You can't be that harsh.
Leave it here
So please go
Take this and go to the great queen mother.
Be sure to buy it
So that our hearts don't get hurt
Please save me, mama
I'm going to go to the middle of the day.
I brought it into the inner hall.
The crown prince's life was sacrificed at Shinjusa Temple.
To praise the hero who saved the day
I tried to take her in as a court lady.
Manufacturing failure for no reason
The court ladies who kicked me out
What comes to mind?
This child who resembles a dead widow
It's as obvious as hell that I'll be kicked out
I was a little considerate of myself.
How
The royal elder
Do you take the royal laws lightly?
law
It's good
Mr. Bin didn't even show up that day.
Without telling you, with my own hands
I opened the bedroom of the Donggung Palace.
If you do it, Mr. Bean too.
Ministers who committed corruption
Everyone deserves to be punished
Everywhere
step by step
Shall we make it a problem?
Mama, the grace that saved my life
Everyone will be in trouble.
That's how it should be
First, she was taken in as a court lady, but
Please bring her to the harem soon.
Yes?
Hu, concubine?
It's not even possible
I can't believe it.
What do you mean?
Still with Mr. Bean
I didn't even do a wedding ceremony.
How come from a concubine?
Are you saying you can take it in?
Besides, this child is now a court lady.
I am afraid of incurring your wrath.
Tsk, man
There are so many things to be afraid of
Is losing one piece of poverty not enough?
This child also has an upper left hand
Are you planning to let him die?
I feel sorry for the poor.
To such a cowardly man
I gave you my heart and then it went away
Mama, you are talking too much.
Even if you're old in the back room, you're still this person
I am the head of this country's internal affairs department.
Do what this person wants!
Would you like to try it?
When I do this, I feel bubbly
Is it falling off little by little?
What does that mean?
What caused a scandal
It's not Woohee?
no, suddenly
Why is the story about Mr. Bean coming out?
I heard that the nephew of the manufacturing palace paid it.
Well, Woohee’s wife said that she was Yeori.
Lord, please
we now
let's never see each other again
I am now
you are so horrible
Ha, what did I do...
Great King Mama
That's too much
no, what
As if you had entrusted me with the position of concubine.
Are you telling me to give it up? Tsk
Because that's why you saved me
To the left wing leader
From what I heard
Well, what is the purpose of treason?
They say you can threaten me
What else is there?
Oh, why, what did you say?
If you scare me
Did you think I would be scared?
I am not
Just take it off and that's it.
If mama says no,
The world will be deceived
one
Mama herself
You can't fool me, can you?
Mama
I don't mean to scare you
I'm proving my worth
Not this decoction bowl
Please look at me who brought this to you.
You are so important
What I have is
I became that close to the crown prince.
Is that what you mean?
yes
Did the Crown Prince say that?
I had you in my heart
Did you say that?
You haven't said anything yet
It's clear that you're being rude
Park Dal-i
I like it
Crown Prince
Park Dal-i
no
He said he likes me so much that he even entrusts me with my contract.
They said they even slept together
But why is she a concubine?
I'm not getting off, but I'm a mistress.
Hmm, maybe that's not it
- 'That'?
- Young people these days
We play tug of war
Why are you suddenly pulling the string?
It's not a real line
It's about pushing and pulling emotions.
It looks like I'm going to push it away
If it seems like it's going to go away, pull it straight
tug of war of love
no
I did it to live, to live
My life is at stake
What can't they do?
No, what, who, who says what?
I like it, I don't like it, I don't like it
What is lukewarm?
Anyway
These days, oh
That's because you didn't go through the trouble, through the trouble, huh?
No, then
If you don't become a concubine,
The Great Queen Mama will...
Can you kill me?
Ah...
The person who needs to be comforted drop by drop
It was me
On the top left of Mr. Bean
To the great queen mother
How many landmines are there, Mr.
Now that land mine
I am the person you should avoid
degradation
This national wedding
- Don't do it.
- Don't worry.
My body will come back before the national wedding.
Until then
I'll have to come back
Even if my body comes back
Don’t do it, you national soul!
What...
With a woman with a bullet in her stomach
It doesn't make sense to become a married couple.
That's why it's so dangerous
It doesn't make sense
It's full of nonsense
Don't do it, this national marriage
If we break this national spirit
The left hand is going to kill me
Bon city
They say the best defense is offense
I need to kill you before I die
Why are you suddenly opening your eyes like that?
Gyesa-nyeon incident, revenge on the lower class
I'll join the map.
Now my body is gone
Not even half of this revenge
Oh my goodness
Yeah
As you commanded
I learned about Bakga Dal-i.
Boryeong Park Gaekju is closed.
Haengsu and his family
disappeared
Is this the crown prince's doing?
That's...
Old man Heo Ok said it.
Why brother?
Bakgadal is that child
I am old man Heo’s niece.
Losing both parents makes it difficult to make a living
Old man Heo lives in Gaekju, Boryeong.
I made it as a backpacker.
- Hey!
- ah!
Mr. Lee
Ouch!
Ugh
What are they doing now!
Thank you, Nari
Until this guy grows up
What should I do if I have to protect it from the cage?
It's going
I have something to check
I need you to move.
I wish I didn't go
dangerously
No, my body
I don't even know when I'll come back
You can't just sit back and wait.
Still
Ah, I wish I could take revenge on the god of war
Han Dae-yu in Gibang?
Wandering around without thinking
The crown prince who goes in and out of the gibang
To deceive the left eye
A more suitable setting is
Where can I be?
Oh, why are you like this?
Don't listen to me, this
Ugh, oh, that's it, oh
Oh no
Ha, in the settings I set
There is no such thing as shabby beauty, right?
Indiscriminately
It's done
Why?
What
corner behind
- degradation
- Oh my.
degradation
Damn, mom, I'm surprised.
Ah, really, why is it always just me?
Look at this, it really annoys me
I'm really annoyed, ugh
Se, Sedol, that...
Well, it's not like that.
Sedol, Sedol, Sedol
Why is that bastard
Come in now, Mr.
degradation
I can't go out today
What does that mean?
Jeundaegun Nari is sick.
Nari
How long can you avoid it?
You probably don't have it
There are less than 50 days left until the national wedding.
Just wait until then
Wouldn't it be okay?
No, by the way, I am Jeundaegun.
Why did you take revenge?
Are you in a relationship with Mr. Bean over there?
Left body passed away due to false accusation
Prince Jeun’s mother
Become a vengeful spirit
It caused the Gyesa Year incident.
So I started a rumor
To hide the burden
That damn bastard messing with your family?
Ah, our Jeundaegun Nari
What should I do because I’m upset?
Hey, you hurt my wounds
Have you ever empathized that much?
Is it just his wounds? Me, me?
Every night, in my dreams
wearing flower shoes
leisurely walking
That kind of life
Welcome
With this, yeah
This one is pretty too, this and this
Wow
um
Wow, you dress up like this.
-You're very pretty.
- Recognition
Wow
No, what does this say?
No, I'm wearing a map like this.
You look just like your precious baby.
Wow, it's really pretty
look straight
how pretty you are
how precious you are
So, huh?
To become a slave
You said you would think of others before yourself.
Stop thinking like that, okay?
Oh my, oh my
It’s so pretty, but on a day like today
You should draw a picture
My younger brother in front of me
I'm drawing a picture
I don't know how good you are at drawing
Because you bought a lot of clothes today
30% as my special treatment
I'll shave it for you
Hey, well, it's not like that.
Well, that's okay.
- Just Gayu
-Let's draw
I'm pretty today
Oh my, yeah
Come on, go.
Ah, what is it?
- huh?
- Well, stick close to me, hmm.
Oh, hmm, I just, okay?
Do that
Ah, really
This didn't work because the paper was too thin.
A small piece of paper and this
What does this have to do with...
No...
Joe, they say the paper is small.
Is there a star, star, star number?
Right? If the paper is small
Well, I guess
Yeah, because the paper is small, small.
Hmm
Okay, let's begin now.
Gombang is over
Let’s take a look at the second pose.
Ah, two minutes
To be honest, it's awkward, yeah
I'm going
Oh, it's from ancient times.
Ha, the third one is our lady
Let's smile brightly like this
Oh, Jiyu?
Ah, the original
I'm not the type of person to get this nervous.
I understand
- Me, me, me, yeah
- Ah
Ah, what are you talking about?
Come on, smile brightly.
Wow, it's pretty
Aegis is so pretty when she smiles
Ah, the last one is just
They both smile brightly
Wow, it's pretty
It was pulled out very well.
Oh, I'm sorry
Ah, these nostrils are paradise.
Making a fuss
Please take care of it.
Is it a fuss or not, huh?
No, no fuss, yeah
That...
Yes, yes
Wow, Mushin smells so good, huh?
Oh, me, me
The scent is a people magazine, ugh
Are you really selling something dangerous?
Oh, no, that can't be possible.
Cosmetics is just an occupational disease.
I smell a strong scent every day
Are you breathing smoke?
Well, my lungs are all ruined.
But until my body breaks down
Why do I keep doing this?
Is your life very difficult?
No, who
I'm going to glue your throat
Would you like to suffocate?
I'm just protecting it.
My grandmother likes the scent
keep your seat
I like my grandmother
guard next to it
It's been 40 years since I lived like that.
The groom must protect his dreams
What if you don't keep it?
It's good, so keep it
Is there any other way?
Wow!
and!
What is this? Wow!
Wow, it's pretty
Look at this!
Wow
After
Hmm, really
What falls on the ground is dirty
What's dirty?
It's just pretty
It's pretty
Spring clears away the snow, but the flower petals
Wow
People clean up
It's all about money and manpower.
Chi, why are you like that?
It feels good to see petals.
Sobok Sobok is made of flower petals.
Why do you feel so good?
They collected the dust and made it into a mountain.
Collecting small clothes made me happy
The term sobok sobok
A small fortune has accumulated
I think I will definitely be happy
Well, I don’t think that’s what you mean, huh?
West
This is it, when you sleep
It's a good scent
There are things I am thankful for and
You enter the palace first.
Chi
What were you doing?
The sound of snow falling
I was listening
Sobok, Sobok
Small blessings pile up like snow
I feel like I will definitely be happy
Isn't it?
After
Please give me your hand
Now
Today's casual and casual clothes.
So pretty
Really
I
I smiled at the other woman.
I dare say it was fun
Without shame
I think it's because they're so similar
Can you please look at me?
What is this...
Ugh, why are you doing this?
Can't you solve this!
Don't lose your strength for no reason
There will still be some energy left
Is it a left injury?
Did Jwasang order you to kill me?
I think it would be better for me too
Do you have anything to check?
Today it's just not noticeable
I only plan to scratch it.
It's a fertility drug.
Conceiving a grandson
It's your only use
When it becomes useless
At the Great King's Vision
They'll try to kill you first
No way
Let go of this, let go of this
No, leave this aside.
Let go of this
Let go...
Flower shoes for the theme
Burn it
To call it a dream
It's grandiose
Not straw shoes
Reasons for living a life wearing flower shoes
No more running away
Just settled down
Making a real family
dare
How dare you!
- Oh my.
- Ugh!
Ugh
Ah...
Ugh!
What are you doing?
get that bitch back
Ugh
Hey!
ah!
Ouch!
Yes you bitch!
Ah, ah...
That bitch...
That, that, that, that toxic bitch
Just because of flower shoes
Bare hands in the fireplace
Not here
I'm about to collapse
Fall down in a safe place
Yabawido, that street
I don't lose people's minds like this
It was a spring breeze in spring and March
When I turn around, the cold wind blows again.
I'm being wronged, aren't I?
huh? Are you tired of me too?
Why are you showing your back to me?
Oh, where are you going?
Aren't I finished talking yet?
Mandeok, Mandeok
Mandeok-ah
Ah
Huh?
Hey, kid, where are you going?
Mandeok-ah
Hey, I’m surprised.
Deterioration?
lowering!
No, what's going on?
No, no, why don't you wear flower shoes?
Hug me like a boss
Wow
No, barefoot, huh?
Ah, what the hell...
Oh, why are your hands like this again?
He said his dream is to wear flower shoes.
Ah, why suddenly
Are you talking about Kkotsin Taryeong again?
The groom must protect his dreams
What if you don't keep it?
It's good, so keep it
Is there any other way?
you
Wear flower shoes
Running barefoot
Because it will be me
Well, what...
Now
I can't pretend not to know
Oh, my dear
degradation
Degradation!
Ah, me, ah, me
In my body now
There's this girl
in my heart
the moon flows
What should I do?
Uh, come to your senses.
Like this
I guess my body has changed
Let me get hurt instead of you
Resembling a ruined bin so much
that face
It's annoying
Get rid of it
You are
You can't protect the moon.
From now on, I am your shield
You hide behind me
You keep saying that.
Nonsense
You start looking forward to it.
Hey, do you like it?